{"keywords": ["birds", "capable of", "fly"], "sentence": "birds can fly.", "general_sentence": "most birds can fly.", "question": "can birds fly?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "birds have wings.", "cot_logic": "Things with lightweight bodies and strong wing muscles can usually fly. Birds have these physical characteristics.", "generic": "birds can fly.", "general_question": "can most birds fly?"}
{"keywords": ["playing tennis", "causes", "feeling relaxed"], "sentence": "playing tennis makes one feel relaxed.", "general_sentence": "playing tennis usually makes one feel relaxed.", "question": "does playing tennis cause someone to feel relaxed?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "tennis is a kind of sport.", "cot_logic": "Sport can make people feel relaxed. Tennis is a kind of sport.", "generic": "playing tennis makes one feel relaxed.", "general_question": "does playing tennis usually makes one feel relaxed?"}
{"keywords": ["rooms", "located at", "buildings"], "sentence": "rooms are located at buildings.", "general_sentence": "rooms are usually located at buildings.", "question": "are rooms located at buildings?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "a room is a part of a building.", "cot_logic": "Rooms are enclosed by walls. Walls enclose the interior of buildings.", "generic": "rooms are in the buildings.", "general_question": "are rooms usually in the buildings?"}
{"keywords": ["fish", "capable of", "sleep"], "sentence": "fish can sleep.", "general_sentence": "fish can sleep.", "question": "can fish sleep?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "fishes are animals.", "cot_logic": "Animals can sleep. Fishes are animals.", "generic": "fish can sleep.", "general_question": "can most fishes sleep?"}
{"keywords": ["sheepskin", "used for", "writing"], "sentence": "sheepskin can be used for writing.", "general_sentence": "sheepskin can be used for writing.", "question": "can sheepskin be used for writing?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "sheepskin is the hide of a sheep.", "cot_logic": "Things with a smooth and consistent surface can be used for writing. Sheepskins have that texture.", "generic": "sheepskins are used for writing.", "general_question": "are sheepskins generally used for writing?"}
{"keywords": ["spicy", "is a", "pain"], "sentence": "spicy is a kind of pain.", "general_sentence": "spicy is a kind of pain.", "question": "is spicy a kind of pain?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "spicy is a feeling of burning and pain.", "cot_logic": "Foods containing pungent compounds irratetes sensations of pain. Spicy foods have pungent compounds.", "generic": "spicy is a kind of pain.", "general_question": "is spicy a kind of pain?"}
{"keywords": ["silicon chip", "made of", "sand"], "sentence": "silicon chips are made of sand.", "general_sentence": "silicon chips are made of sand.", "question": "is silicon chip made of sand?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "sand contains silicon.", "cot_logic": "Silicon chips are made of silicon. Silicon is a chemical element that is found in sand.", "generic": "silicon chips are made of sand.", "general_question": "are silicon chips generally made of sand?"}
{"keywords": ["typhoon", "similar to", "hurricane"], "sentence": "typhoons are similar to hurricanes.", "general_sentence": "generally, typhoons are similar to hurricanes.", "question": "is typhoon similar to hurricane?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "typhoon is a type of cyclone.", "cot_logic": "Hurricanes and typhoons are both tropical cyclones. Tropical cyclones are similar in nature.", "generic": "typhoon is similar to hurricane.", "general_question": "are typhoons generally similar to hurricanes?"}
{"keywords": ["water", "has property", "transparent"], "sentence": "water is transparent.", "general_sentence": "water is usually transparent.", "question": "is water transparent?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "water is an inorganic, odorless, and colorless substance.", "cot_logic": "Transparent substances allow light to pass through them without scattering it. Water allows light to pass through it without scattering it.", "generic": "water is transparent.", "general_question": "is water usually transparent?"}
{"keywords": ["cell phone", "used to", "call someone"], "sentence": "cell phones can be used to call someone.", "general_sentence": "generally, cell phones can be used to call someone.", "question": "can cell phones be used to call someone?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "cell phone can be used for communication.", "cot_logic": "Cell phones are used to make phone calls. Phone calls are made to communicate with someone.", "generic": "cell phones can be used to call someone.", "general_question": "can cell phones usually be used to call someone?"}
{"keywords": ["bamboo", "is a", "grass"], "sentence": "bamboo is a type of grass.", "general_sentence": "bamboo is a type of grass.", "question": "is bamboo a type of grass?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "bamboo is a gramineous plant.", "cot_logic": "Bamboo belongs to the family Poaceae. Poaceae is a family of grasses.", "generic": "bamboo is a kind of grass.", "general_question": "is bamboo a kind of grass?"}
{"keywords": ["oasis", "capable of", "provide life"], "sentence": "oases can provide life.", "general_sentence": "oases are generally capable of providing life.", "question": "can oasis provide life?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "an oasis is an small patch of vegetation surrounded by desert.", "cot_logic": "Oases are areas of vegetation and water in deserts. Vegetation and water are essential for life in derserts.", "generic": "oases can provide life.", "general_question": "can oases generally provide life?"}
{"keywords": ["people", "desires", "relax after work"], "sentence": "people want to relax after work.", "general_sentence": "people usually want to relax after work.", "question": "do people want to relaxed after work?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "people will be tired after work.", "cot_logic": "Tired people want to relax. Work makes people tired.", "generic": "people want to relax after work.", "general_question": "do people usually want to relax after work?"}
{"keywords": ["computer", "has a", "chip"], "sentence": "computers have chips.", "general_sentence": "computers usually have chips.", "question": "do computers have chips?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "chips are needed for computing.", "cot_logic": "Computers contain microprocessors. Microprocessors are a type of chips.", "generic": "computers have chips.", "general_question": "do computers generally have chips?"}
{"keywords": ["fish", "has a", "ears"], "sentence": "fishes have ears.", "general_sentence": "fishes have ears.", "question": "do fishes have ears?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "fishes can hear.", "cot_logic": "Things can hear have ears. Fishes can hear.", "generic": "fishes have ears.", "general_question": "do fishes generally have ears?"}
{"keywords": ["basketball players", "desires", "winning"], "sentence": "basketball players want to win.", "general_sentence": "most basketball players want to win.", "question": "do basketball players want to win?", "answer": "yes", "cot_fact": "athletes usually desire winning in competitions.", "cot_logic": "Winning is an important goal for many athletes. Basketball players are athletes", "generic": "basketball players want to win.", "general_question": "do basketball players usually want to win?"}